let MCQS = [{
    question: "What is the name of Todoroki's quirk?",
    choice1: "Half-Cold Half-Hot",
    choice2: "Half-Hot Half-Cold",
    choice3: "Half-Ice Half-Fire",
    choice4: "Half and Half",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "How many siblings does Todoroki have?",
    choice1: "2",
    choice2: "3",
    choice3: "4",
    choice4: "1",
    answer: 1
},
            {
            question: "How did Todoroki get his scar?",
    choice1: "An accident with his mom.",
    choice2: "A fight against a villain.",
    choice3: "no reason",
    choice4: "powers gone wrong",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "Why didn't Todoroki like using his fire powers?",
    choice1: "dad issues",
    choice2: "was scared of fire",
    choice3: "hated sand",
    choice4: "too coool for that",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "How did Todoroki get ito U.A. High School?",
    choice1: "Reccommendation",
    choice2: "grades",
    choice3: "passed a test",
    choice4: "lotto",
    answer: 0
},
            {
            question: "What covered half of Todoroki's first hero costume?",
    choice1: "fire",
    choice2: "ice",
    choice3: "gravel",
    choice4: "smiley faces",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "How did Todoroki rank among those recommended to U.A. that year??",
    choice1: "1st",
    choice2: "3rd",
    choice3: "2nd",
    choice4: "4th",
    answer: 2
},{
               question: "Who finally convinced Todoroki to use his fire powers?",
    choice1: "himself",
    choice2: "Deku",
    choice3: "Momo Yaoyorozu",
    choice4: "Katsuki Bakugo",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Who did Todoroki do his hero internship with?",
    choice1: "All Might",
    choice2: "His DAd",
    choice3: "hawks",
    choice4: "Gran Torino",
    answer: 1
},
            {
               question: "Who did Todoroki team up with for his final exams?",
    choice1: "Minoru Mineta",
    choice2: "Izuku Midoriya",
    choice3: "Fumikage Tokoyami",
    choice4: "Momo Yaoyorozu",
    answer: 3
}];